

DESIRÉ M **CARMONA**

UX-UI · DESIGNER · DEVELOPER · WRITER · TEACHER · HUMAN

email

work@desiremcarmona.com

web desiremcarmona.com **blog** galuxui.com.es porfolio Bëhance



in My LinkedIn

PROFILE

UX-UI specialist, designer, developer, instructor for LinkedIn Learning, mentor and teacher.

Active speaker, writing guides and articles in ENG|SPA for the tech community in my blog and webpage. Previously in **#SmartCities**, **#Education** and now trying to **#getBetter!**

Passionate for videogames, culture, society and sharing knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

HACK A BOSS | 03/2020 ~ 09/2020

Bootcamp teacher, web designer, web developer.

MentorCruise | 02/2020 ~ 08/2020

Mentor for design/UX/UI. Volunteer.

LinkedIn Learning | 04/2019 ~

Instructor.

iNMovens Solutions S.L. | 4 months

Web/App designer, web developer.

Atos | 1 year

UX/UI, design&dev in Smart City projects. See Urban Data Platform.

EDUCATION

Graphic Design

Seeway Barcelona, 2019

Web design&confection

Escola Antoni Algueró, 2017

Videogames, animation and programming (first year only)

CEV Barcelona, 2017-2018

TECH PROJECTS

SCSS-MEDIAQ

A scss npm package I did.

Dealingarden

Vuejs, SASS, CheapShark API, Vue-Headful.

InfoCoin

Vuejs, SASS, Coincap API.

Vuédex

Vuejs, SASS, PokéAPI, Vue-headful.

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Freelancer | 3 years

Writer, translator, designer, developer

Colossus Gaming Cup | 7 months

Founder, president, manager

El Tinyol | 9 years

Store Manager

LANGUAGES

Spanish, Catalan

Native

English

Advanced, fluent

SKILLS

Tasha

| recns | | Other | |
|------------|-------|------------|-----------|
| HTML, CSS | AXIOS | ux / uı | Writing |
| JavaScript | APIs | Prototypes | Marketing |
| Vuejs | NPM | Sketches | Pixel art |
| SASS, SCSS | C# | Github | Bulma CSS |

Wireframes

Software

JS Libraries

Adobe XD, Sketch, InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Figma, Webflow, Unity

OTHER PROJECTS

One of my LinkedIn Learning courses

App Design for PlatziCollab

Website concept design

Illustration Design Sample